선데이 아이스크림을 주문하는데 하루는
Cream sundae for himself, and then offers one
? 빈 의자를 옆에 놓아달라고 주문했어.
To the empty stool sitting next to him.
한참동안은 이렇게 주문했는데
This goes on for a while
주인에 도대체 뭐하냐고 물을때까지 말이야
Until the owner finally asks him what he's doing.
이 남자가 말하길 " 저는 물리학자입니다."
The man says, "well, I'm a physicist,
"그리고 양자역학은
and quantum mechanics...
이 의자의 물질이 즉각적으로
Teaches us "that it is possible
아름다운 여자로 변해서 내 제안을
For the matter above this stool "to
받아들이고 나와 사랑에
Spontaneously turn into a beautiful woman
빠질거라고 알려준답니다."
Who might accept my offer and fall in love with me."
주인이 말하길 "많은 싱글들이,
The owner then says, "well, lots of single,
"아름다운여자들이 우리 가게에 오는데 .
"beautiful women come in here ever day.
"그 여자들한테 아이스크림 하나 사주지 그러쇼?
"why don't you buy an ice cream for one of them,
그래야 당신과 사랑에 빠질텐데요?"
And they might fall in love with you?"
그러자 물리학자 왈,
And the physicist says, "yeah, but what